Threatened by a ruthless demon, humanity was on the brink of destruction.
All seemed lost until a lone mage stepped forward and took up the fight.
After his trials, he was hailed as the Wizard King, and his story became legend.
Here we go!
Onward, the Chateau de Verre!
It's over! You're going down!
Asta and Yuno joined forces to drive back the attacks of Klaus and Hammond.
Thick!
Meanwhile, the real Ligt have been preparing to make his move.
The real Ligt have been preparing to make his move.
The real Ligt have been preparing for the fight.
Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Hall Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow Wow
以及
I'll see you next time.
See you next time.
I can't find an opening. Time to change my approach.
Not yet.
All right. My turn.
Monozone.
Spirit Storm.
I'm not done yet.
Who are these two?
You're not killing Yunu!
For us to either!
He's my rival!
He blocked it with that sword?
He's condensing a huge amount of magic.
Is this Yunu's spell?
Oh...
Ah...
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaah!
The giant hole you just made in the ceiling does kind of brighten up the place.
But you lost your grimoire, and both of your swords with it.
You sure that was a good move?
Guess he's not in a talking mood.
Well, never mind the grimoire.
It isn't mine anymore.
What?
Raya, let's go.
Ligt is finally here for real now.
That's all that matters.
What is that weirdo's problem?
You know soaking wet now.
You better not have given me a cold.
Next time we meet, I'm going to sneeze on you.
Zora.
This way.
There's another captain here.
They're fine.
They're just unconscious.
Hello there, Raya.
Hey, Otto.
How's everything been?
Not bad, thanks.
Is he still...
Yeah.
Looks like all we can do is wait for him to awaken the rest of the way.
I suppose.
So where are the others?
One moment.
It's been quite a while, hasn't it?
Five whole centuries.
But all of you look great.
Well, about that time.
Let's go pay the rest of our friends a visit.
And then, we'll wipe out all humankind.
I blacked out!
Well, for some weird reason, my whole body hurts and I'm dripping wet too.
What's wrong with me?
I liked it better when you were knocked out.
You're gonna burst my eardrums, you big dumb idiot!
Who you calling?
Gah!
My ears hurt too!
This is the worst!
You survived!
I'm so relieved.
Yeah.
I'm glad we're all okay.
Hey, where'd the hideout go?
Crazy as it may sound,
it took off toward the royal capital while you were out cold.
What do you mean it took off?
Like how?
You came back alive just like you promised.
You're the luckiest damn half-pint I know.
How's the captain-
Gah!
She's unconscious, but she'll pull through.
That's good news at least.
She won't be up anytime soon, though.
I'd wake her, but I don't have a death wish.
You made it.
This is wonderful.
Mushroom Man and the Silver Eagles, Captain-
Gah!
Two of our comrades seem to have changed sides.
Fortunately, we were able to escape using my mushroom smoke screen and the mobility boost from Nozel's magic.
Really?
Them two-
Ow!
You guys eat, too!
Sure!
Nah, I'll pass.
You really shouldn't eat those raw.
You'll get a tummy ache.
I know these'll probably make me sick, but Asta gave them to me.
I can't let them go to waste!
Here, use this.
Magic item, Alia's booth.
This tool provides an enormous enhancement to the body's natural healing abilities, which you three desperately need.
Oh, that's great!
Thank you!
Awesome!
The pain's already going away!
What a useful magic item!
Thank you so much for your help!
Nozel's a pretty decent guy, but I don't know how he can see with that haircut.
Hold still, Yuno!
Let me take away your pain!
And give it to you!
Hey, I don't want it!
Are you feeling better, my darling?
Yeah.
Oh, thank goodness!
You guys!
You're all okay!
Noelle!
And she brought that.
It's your big brother!
What happened to you, Kirsch?
Man, you look like crap!
Even spotted with blood, I'm still beautiful.
I don't think so.
I'm such a gorgeously fragile flower.
Okay, who is this nutball?
Noelle!
Where's the team?
I don't know how to explain all this, but luck turned on us.
Oh, that sucks!
That Crimson Lion as well.
Same with Klaus and Hammond.
It was out of nowhere.
Don't forget Rill.
This is bad.
They're pitiful.
Hey!
You have markings on your face too!
Are you sure you're okay?
I'm the same person I was.
My magic's just been boosted a bit.
All right, fine.
I guess I can spell it out.
How dare you condescend me!
I'm royalty after all.
Oh yeah?
Well, I'm the wind spirit, so you're nothing special, missy.
No one asked you.
The spatial mage who was on standby isn't here.
He must have changed sides like they did.
Captain Nozel!
Come in!
Can you hear me?
What's wrong?
Oh good, you're there.
I thought I would never get through.
What's that?
A magic transmission device that all of the captains have.
Several of our squad members have suddenly become violent.
They're acting strange and claiming to be elves.
The worst part is, their magic power is much stronger than usual.
We can't handle them alone.
Apparently, the other squads are experiencing the same thing.
Something must be taking over the kingdom.
What was that?
Answer me!
Is this happening all over the place?
It's not looking good, I know that much.
Come what may, we're still magic knights.
Which means our number one responsibility is to protect the Clover Kingdom.
Even if doing so means we have to eliminate some of our own comrades in the process.
And even if it comes at the cost of our lives.
But luck...
When he attacked me before, his spell didn't hit me.
I missed you.
Yeah, looks like I've gotten a little rusty.
Let's try again.
He was moving extremely quickly.
But we were still able to get away from him.
I think luck made that happen.
Well then, why did he hit me?
I'm sure you deserved it.
That means, luck's soul is fighting to resist.
Just like Yuno still has control.
And since we know that's possible, we should be able to restore everyone's free will.
There has to be a way.
As magic knights, we can save our squad mates and the Clover Kingdom.
Yeah.
Let's do it.
Alright!
Go!
What do you think that is?
As soon as those lightswords go away, now this happens?
Why is the demon skull glowing?
It's frightening.
Hey, see that?
Huh?
What's happening this time?
It looks like daybreak.
Nuh-uh.
Not that.
Something's coming.
No.
It's headed for the capital.
But what is it?
Those are my friends, of course.
His friends?
Look at his clothes. He's dressed like her.
Your robe tells me you're a magic knight.
It would appear that you humans have rapidly increased in number over the last several centuries.
Sir?
The people who possess the least magic power make their homes in this area.
And then, as you reach the center, you begin to encounter the stronger inhabitants.
I see your kind continues to discriminate in petty ways.
So magic knight? Or not?
Kinda looks like he is.
And you weaklings are the target of this prejudice.
You humans. So arbitrary.
What?
Hold on. Who are you exactly?
We do not discriminate.
We slaughter all humans.
Equally and swiftly.
Poison plant magic.
Now, Zoffner's garden of lingering burns.
Oh yeah! I'm as good as new!
Hey! Where'd your shirt go?
I had to get a good look and make sure my injuries are healed.
Okay, now you know, so get dressed already!
Now that I've recovered, my beauty can shine to the fullest!
I kinda wish you hadn't recovered at all.
The captain should be better too, right?
I don't understand why she's not waking up.
Just let her rest.
Oh yeah! You can have this back now!
Throw it out. It only works once.
Whoa, seriously?
I mean, it's kinda cool looking, so I think I'll hang on to it.
Do what you want.
We're almost to the Forsaken Realm.
What's wrong?
Someone's attacking that area.
But that's...
The village!
You know when I grew up there, we have to help!
No.
We must proceed directly to the capital as quickly as possible.
The best way to protect Clover Kingdom is to secure the most populated area first.
My hometown is part of this kingdom!
You two may do as you see fit, but we press on.
That said, you're both crucial to our fighting strength.
Finish quickly and meet us in the capital.
Right!
Let me go with them!
You'll remain with us, Noelle.
You're forcing me?
You are royalty.
I order you to accompany me to safeguard the castle.
You want my help? Really?
Although, if we're being honest, your very existence is pointless.
This is no place for a pathetic creature like you.
Now leave.
Right!
Then I'll go!
I had always found it strange.
Why did I possess poisoned plant magic?
It didn't seem logical, but one day I understood.
It hurts so much!
Help me!
Please!
It feels like my whole body is being burned alive!
That's what this magic is for.
Eradicating insignificant lives like yours.
Water creation magic!
Holy fist of a lock!
No life is insignificant!
Not one!
No, Father!
Hang in there!
So some of you are able to use a little magic at least.
Or is it only you?
Are you of noble blood?
Well, no matter.
Even the mightiest of humans are powerless against the elves.
Who is this guy?
He's a monster!
You're so cruel, hurting a priest like that!
Listen, I don't know what happened in your past.
But what did the residents of this poor village ever do to you?
We live simple, peaceful lives like anyone else!
You'll be okay!
I'll make all the alleys disappear!
We cry.
God!
This is way too confusing!
We struggle.
At this rate, I don't know how we'll make it through the winter.
We worry.
And yet...
Pot potatoes again?
At least we have enough food.
Yeah!
I love pot potatoes!
You make the tastiest dishes out of these, sister.
I don't mind eating yours, Nash.
No way!
I still want them!
Food is food!
Need water!
We find a way to laugh.
And dream.
And live life with everything we've got!
We don't deserve to die like this!
Nobody in the kingdom does!
Yeah.
You're poor like the rest of us.
Orphaned cast-off.
Kids like us don't get to have dreams.
Hey, Nash...
No giving up!
You hear me?!
We can dream as much as we want to!
Even if you're a poor orphan, you can become great just like anyone else.
You can do anything you want, make your dreams come true, and make the people you care about happy!
That's exactly what I'm going to prove!
If by some chance, some very small one, you actually manage to join the Magic Knights?
Yeah, what?
Then I'll start believing dreams really can come true!
That I can be anything I want!
And maybe one day I'll become a Magic Knight too!
Or, you know, whatever.
Without me and Yuno here, guess you're going to be the biggest brother from now on!
Keep these guys safe!
We're counting on you, Nash!
I agree.
No one's life should have to end in sadness.
Therefore, I'll wipe out the source of that sadness.
Your kind.
Poisoned flat magic.
Softness garden of lingering burns.
No!
Leave her alone!
Stop!
Oh no!
Stay back!
Ah!
Asta!
Yuno!
Father, wake up!
It's Asta!
He's back!
And Yuno too!
You're really brave, Nash.
Good job!
You mean it!
Thanks a lot, guys!
Stay back!
It's our turn now!
We'll be right back!
I don't need no money.
I don't need no魔力は要らない.
自力で挑んだミラクル起きること願い.
微力ながら1ミリずつビリビリ切り込んでく.
世界を巻き込んでく.
My disabilities, my ability.
逆にそれが俺のエネルギー.
どうしても自らを見失って嫌いになって.
負けそうになったら.
Just cry out loud.
傷つく音に.
立ち向かう勇気へと導いてく.
Our treasure.
裏切らないのは.
最高に.
There is love.
かざしたちがい光が生きる treasure.
ご視聴ありがとうございました。
CLOVERECLESS
Exploring the vowels with Kirsch.
The first vowel.
A
As in, awfully gorgeous.
I
As in, intense beauty.
You
U
Ultra chic.
E
EK
Exquisite.
Oh
Ornate
As in, observe the ornateness of my overwhelmingly oculent.
Oh,As in, overly obnoxious oculent.
Oh my goodness,it's just too much.
I'll take it from here.
I don't know who you are,but I'll never let you put the people of Haj Village in harm's way.
Your time is up.
Black Clover, page 102.
Two Miracles.
When are these weird markings gonna go away?